So we have our binary moon data,
我们已经有了二元 Moon Data
and the next thing we want to do is define and train a custom PyTorch model.
下一步是定义和训练一个自定义 PyTorch 模型
Specifically, a neural network that performs binary classification.
即一个执行二元分类的神经网络
Now, aside from this exercise notebook,
除了这个练习 notebook 之外
I've given you a source directory here.
这里还有一个 source 目录
Inside here, you'll find several files,
其中有三个文件
train.py, predict.py, and model.py.
分别是 train.py predict.py 和 model.py
Model.py will be where the layers of a PyTorch model will be explicitly defined.
我们将在 model.py 中明确定义 PyTorch 模型的层级
Predict.py is completely provided to you.
我们已经提供了完整的 predict.py
You won't need to change anything in here.
你不需要更改任何地方
It's complete and just applies
它已经是完整的文件
a trained model to some data and returns predicted class scores.
可以直接将训练过的模型应用到数据上并返回预测的类别分数
Finally, we have train.py which is
最后是 train.py 文件
where I'll be demonstrating how to build and train a custom model.
我将在其中演示如何构建和训练自定义模型
So let's take this piece by piece.
我们一步步地来
Your first task will be to define a simple binary classifier in model.py.
你的第一个任务是在 model.py 中定义一个简单的二元分类器
In the notebook, I've specified that this model should
我在 notebook 中指出
accept a number of input_dim features.
这个模型的参数是 input_dim 特征的数量
It should then process this input through a couple of hidden layers,
然后将这个输入传入几个隐藏层
and return a single output value that indicates
并返回一个输出值
a class score close to zero or close to one,
表示接近 0 或 1 的类别分数
for our purple and for our yellow points respectively.
分别对应紫点和黄点
In fact, this output value should be a sigmoid-activated class score.
实际上 这个输出值应该是 S 型激活类别分数
You can even display the model.py contents in the notebook.
你甚至可以在 notebook 中显示 model.py 的内容
This is the starting code I've given you for this model.py file.
这是我为你提供的 model.py 文件起始代码
Let me click on that file directly.
直接点击该文件
So all your tasks are marked as TODOs in this file.
所有任务在此文件中都标记为 TODO
In the init function,
在 init 函数中
you should define a two or three layer model that takes in some number of input features,
你应该定义一个两层或三层的模型 参数包括输入特征的数量
creates hidden layers according to this hidden dimension,
根据此隐藏维度创建隐藏层
and produces an output_dim number of outputs.
并生成 output_dim 个输出
You specify all your layers in this init function,
请在此 init 函数中指定所有层级
and then define the feedforward behavior of the network in forward.
然后在 forward 函数中指定网络的前馈行为
Don't forget to apply activation functions where necessary,
别忘了在必要的位置应用激活函数
and really think about how you might create a binary classifier,
并思考如何创建一个输出 0 或 1 标签的
the outputs a zero or one label.
二元分类器
There're even more details in the notebook,
Notebook 中有很多详情
and a link to an example for a three layer network.
并提供了三层网络示例的链接
So try to complete this model.py file before moving on to the solution and next files.
请先尝试完成此 model.py 文件 然后再查看解答和后续文件